<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2015 Miranda Fluharty

This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/> -->
<resources>
    <string name="help_main_title">Blipsqueak Help</string>
    <string name="help_main">
        Blipsqueak allows you to set different notification\u00A0sounds
        for different types of messages by creating profiles that scan the text of
        incoming\u00A0notifications for certain patterns and playing an associated sound
        if the pattern is matched.
        \n\n
        First, Blipsqueak has to have access to read your notifications. Then, you can choose
        which apps will trigger the custom sounds. Set up a few profiles with patterns and sounds
        and then wait for notifications to come in or test your profiles directly.
        \n\n
        To prevent your notifications from triggering multiple sounds simultaneously, you can either
        set each selected app\'s notifications to be silent or delay Blipsqueak\'s notifications
        by a second or two in settings.
        \n\n
        More detailed help is available on other screens, or feel free to use the "Contact" option
        if you have any questions.
    </string>
    <string name="help_applist_title">Selected Apps Help</string>
    <string name="help_applist">
        Only apps that are selected here will be able to trigger Blipsqueak\u00A0sounds. Blipsqueak scans
        the text from their notifications to see if it matches any of the profiles you\'ve set up.
    </string>
    <string name="help_bliplist_title">Profile List Help</string>
    <string name="help_bliplist">
        This is the list of all the profiles you\'ve created. Tap the floating action button to add a
        profile, drag the handles to reorder, and swipe from left to right to delete.
        \n\n
        Order matters: messages are scanned against each profile in the order listed here, and the first
        one that matches is triggered. Organize them from specific to general for the best results.
        \n\n
        If you want Blipsqueak to make a default\u00A0sound when notifications don\'t match the rest of
        your profiles, make the very last profile on your list match any message and set your
        default\u00A0sound there.
    </string>
    <string name="help_detail_title">Profile Creation Help</string>
    <string name="help_detail">
        To add your own sounds to the list:
        \n\n
        Find or make a folder called \"Notifications\" on your SD card or built-in storage, then
        copy any sound files you wish to use as notifications into it. Android supports mp3, wav,
        m4a, and ogg file types.
        \n\n\n
        \"Match all patterns\" will only match messages where all of the profile\'s patterns match
        \n\n
        \"Match any pattern\" requires only one pattern to match
        \n\n\n
        Pattern types:
        \n\n
        - contains or does not contain word/phrase: matches messages which contain or don\'t contain
        the exact given word or phrase with word boundaries on either side (for example, \"no\" would
        only match the whole word \"no\" and not any other word containing it such as \"snow\")
        \n\n
        - contains or does not contain character sequence: matches messages which contain or do not
        contain the exact given sequence of characters - whether it\'s a whole word or not (in this
        case, \"no\" would match \"snow\") - use this option to match emoji
        \n\n
        - starts with/ends with: matches messages that start or end with the exact given sequence of
        characters
        \n\n
        - number of words/characters: matches messages that have the given number of words or
        characters (use one number to match exactly that many words/characters or two numbers
        separated by a comma to match any number of words/characters between those two - you can
        even use \",4\" for less than 4 or \"6,\" for more than six)
        \n\n
        - matches exactly: matches only messages whose content is exactly the given text
        \n\n
        - matches any message: will match a message no matter the text (used to set a default sound
        when no other profiles are matched)
        \n\n
        - matches regular expression: matches messages that match the given Java regular expression
        (advanced, see the Java regular expression documentation for more details)
    </string>
</resources>